# **Wayne Parker**

137 Bonney Court • Bridgewater, NJ 08807 908.209.6726 • wayne@wayneparker.biz

# **Summary**

I'm a versatile web development and digital media professional with a broad range of technical, UI/UX and design skills and 15+ years experience in corporate marketing and employee communications. I've worked closely with clients to meet their diverse communications needs, while ensuring consistency with brand standards and marketing strategy.

## Skills

#### **Web Development**

- Designed, built and supported dozens of corporate intranet sites for the Business Marketing organization of the nation's largest telecom firm, utilizing modern web technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, Sass, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, Bootstrap, Bourbon Neat, etc.
- Designed and built mobile web apps to support major corporate events, including the 2014
  Industry Analyst Summit

#### **Other Digital Media**

- Designed and produced printed and electronic materials, including HTML emails, event collateral (print and PDF), sales brochures, posters, and large-scale environmental graphics
- Created animated, interactive, web presentations and applications using Adobe Flash
- Edited and processed audio and video in support of my web and animation projects

# Miscellany

- Technical point-of-contact for my team for workstation, networking and server issues
- Excellent writing and proofreading skills

# History

2011–present	Senior Digital Media Developer, AT&T Business Multimedia Solutions, Bedminster NJ
2003-2010	Digital Media Developer, AT&T Creative Services, Bedminster, NJ
1997-2002	Web Developer, AT&T Employee Communications, Basking Ridge NJ
1996-1997	2D/3D Digital Illustrator and Modeller, Lucent Industrial Design Studio, Whippany NJ
1994-1996	Digital Pre-Press Artist, QLM Marketing, Princeton NJ
1988-1994	Senior Engineer, Northrop Aerospace, Pico Rivera CA

### **Education**

B.Sc. Mechanical Engineering, Georgia Institute of Technology, 1984